<?xml version="1.1" encoding="utf-8"?>
<provider>
  <source>GetGigs</source>
  <generated_date>2023-06-13T19:10:51.903Z</generated_date>
  <job>
    <id><![CDATA[dabc666b-83cd-4447-aa70-2393444868f0]]></id>
    <title><![CDATA[Amazon Warehouse Worker - Day Shifts]]></title>
    <employer><![CDATA[Amazon Warehouse]]></employer>
    <employer_logo></employer_logo>
    <description><![CDATA[Amazon Sortation Center Warehouse Associate<strong>Job Overview</strong><br/>You’ll be part of the dedicated Amazon team that is the first stop on the journey from the warehouse. Our fast-paced, physical roles take place in a sortation center. You will be sorting, scanning, and stacking packages on pallets, helping to get customer orders ready for delivery. Because most of the shifts are part-time, you are in control of your schedule — choose shifts that work best for you now and adjust your schedule in the future, as needed.]]></description>
    <posted_date><![CDATA[2023-05-31T11:12:41.952606Z]]></posted_date>
    <location>
      <zipcode><![CDATA[80261]]></zipcode>
      <city><![CDATA[Denver]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[CO]]></state>
    </location>
    <category><![CDATA[stockers and order fillers]]></category>
    <discipline><![CDATA[logistics]]></discipline>
    <employment_type><![CDATA[full_time]]></employment_type>
    <apply_method><![CDATA[website]]></apply_method>
    <apply_value><![CDATA[https://dev.getgigs.co/jobs/dabc666b-83cd-4447-aa70-2393444868f0]]></apply_value>
    <updated_datetime><![CDATA[2023-05-31T11:12:41.952606Z]]></updated_datetime>
    <workplace_type><![CDATA[on_site]]></workplace_type>
    <shift_type><![CDATA[day_shift]]></shift_type>
    <wage>
      <type><![CDATA[fixed_amount]]></type>
      <rate><![CDATA[hourly]]></rate>
      <minimum><![CDATA[16]]></minimum>
    </wage>
    <benefits></benefits>
  </job>
  <job>
    <id><![CDATA[c39ab57a-b265-4ea8-aba6-7b7221c2a065]]></id>
    <title><![CDATA[Server Design Engineer Secaucus NJ]]></title>
    <employer><![CDATA[ZT Systems</employer>
    <employer_logo></employer_logo>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><b>Why ZT Systems</b></p><p>At ZT Systems, you’ll get to do work you are proud of alongside smart, passionate people. Every day, there are opportunities to collaborate with the best in the industry to design, build, and deliver impactful solutions to world-class customers. Along the way, you will gain hands-on experience in a face-paced environment that’s challenging, rewarding, and career-defining.</p><p>A culture built around our values, we work hard and think fast. We view challenges as opportunities—to do better, push harder, and be faster than we were the day before. When we fail, we learn from it and move on together. And when we succeed we use the momentum to go even further. We create value with everything we do, building the foundation of today—and transforming the future of tomorrow.</p><p>Join ZT Systems and help us build technology infrastructure that connects the world.</p>]]></description>
    <posted_date><![CDATA[2023-06-02T18:03:26.969055Z]]></posted_date>
    <location>
      <zipcode><![CDATA[11697]]></zipcode>
      <city><![CDATA[Breezy Point]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[NY]]></state>
    </location>
    <category><![CDATA[server]]></category>
    <discipline><![CDATA[hospitality]]></discipline>
    <employment_type>f<![CDATA[ull_time]]></employment_type>
    <apply_method><![CDATA[website]]></apply_method>
    <apply_value><![CDATA[https://dev.getgigs.co/jobs/c39ab57a-b265-4ea8-aba6-7b7221c2a065]]></apply_value>
    <updated_datetime><![CDATA[2023-06-02T18:03:26.969055Z]]></updated_datetime>
    <workplace_type><![CDATA[on_site]]></workplace_type>
    <shift_type><![CDATA[day_shift]]></shift_type>
    <wage>
      <type><![CDATA[fixed_amount]]></type>
      <rate><![CDATA[hourly]]></rate>
      <minimum><![CDATA[16]]></minimum>
    </wage>
    <benefits></benefits>
  </job>
  <job>
    <id><![CDATA[745896cb-3564-4557-93a2-cf870fc69dff]]></id>
    <title><![CDATA[Store Supervisor]]></title>
    <employer><![CDATA[iAnthus]]></employer>
    <employer_logo></employer_logo>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Do you have what it takes to be a part of an industry leading cannabis company?</p><p>Be. and its family of companies are positioned to become one of the largest and most trusted chains of medical marijuana companies. Working hand-in-hand with state and local governments, the Be. brand features company-grown, tested, safe, and effective medical marijuana products.</p>]]></description>
    <posted_date><![CDATA[2023-06-02T16:53:32.656043Z]]></posted_date>
    <location>
      <zipcode><![CDATA[12545]]></zipcode>
      <city><![CDATA[Millbrook]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[NY]]></state>
    </location>
    <category><![CDATA[staff manager]]></category>
    <discipline><![CDATA[retail]]></discipline>
    <employment_type><![CDATA[full_time]]></employment_type>
    <apply_method><![CDATA[website]]></apply_method>
    <apply_value><![CDATA[https://dev.getgigs.co/jobs/745896cb-3564-4557-93a2-cf870fc69dff]]></apply_value>
    <updated_datetime><![CDATA[2023-06-03T16:53:32.656043Z]]></updated_datetime>
    <workplace_type><![CDATA[on_site]]></workplace_type>
    <shift_type><![CDATA[day_shift]]></shift_type>
    <wage>
      <type><![CDATA[fixed_amount]]></type>
      <rate><![CDATA[hourly]]></rate>
      <minimum><![CDATA[19]]></minimum>
    </wage>
    <benefits></benefits>
  </job>
  <job>
    <id><![CDATA[1138453a-a259-45d8-9c12-92f4daeea2e5]]></id>
    <title><![CDATA[Front Desk Team Member / Metairie Clinic]]></title>
    <employer><![CDATA[ChenMed]]></employer>
    <employer_logo></employer_logo>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><b>We’re unique. You should be, too.</b></p><p></p><p>We’re changing lives every day.  For both our patients and our team members. Are you innovative and entrepreneurial minded? Is your work ethic and ambition off the charts?  Do you inspire others with your kindness and joy?</p><p></p><p>We’re different than most primary care providers. We’re rapidly expanding and we need great people to join our team.</p><p></p>The Care Facilitator is one of a patient’s first contact with our ChenMed family and, as such, serves as a patient advocate delivering and providing exceptional customer service. The incumbent in this role checks patients in to and out of the medical clinic and provides basic secretarial and administrative support. A successful Care Facilitator possesses a strong commitment to providing superior service and views every interaction as an opportunity to build a trusting relationship with the patient.]]></description>
    <posted_date><![CDATA[2023-05-03T16:10:32.656043Z]]></posted_date>
    <location>
      <zipcode><![CDATA[70006]]></zipcode>
      <city><![CDATA[Metairie]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[LA]]></state>
    </location>
    <category><![CDATA[staff manager]]></category>
    <discipline><![CDATA[healthcare]]></discipline>
    <employment_type><![CDATA[full_time]]></employment_type>
    <apply_method><![CDATA[website]]></apply_method>
    <apply_value><![CDATA[https://dev.getgigs.co/jobs/1138453a-a259-45d8-9c12-92f4daeea2e5]]></apply_value>
    <updated_datetime><![CDATA[2023-06-03T16:53:32.656043Z]]></updated_datetime>
    <workplace_type><![CDATA[on_site]]></workplace_type>
    <shift_type><![CDATA[day_shift]]></shift_type>
    <wage>
      <type><![CDATA[fixed_amount]]></type>
      <rate><![CDATA[hourly]]></rate>
      <minimum><![CDATA[19]]></minimum>
    </wage>
    <benefits></benefits>
  </job>
  <job>
    <id><![CDATA[efbaf799-27ae-4a9e-8178-73fd2fdc0daf]]></id>
    <title><![CDATA[Line Cook]]></title>
    <employer><![CDATA[Sal's Gumbo Shack]]></employer>
    <employer_logo></employer_logo>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Sal's Gumbo Shack is seeking an experienced Line Cook to join our team. As a Line Cook, you will play a pivotal role in crafting and delivering delicious food to the greater Long Beach community.</p><p><strong>Gig Summary:</strong></p><ul><li><p>$15.50 - $16/hr</p></li><li><p>Part-Time Line Cook (20-24 hrs weekly)</p><p><strong>Apply if you:</strong></p></li></ul><ul><li><p>Have at least 1 year of relevant experience in a fast-paced kitchen environment</p></li><li><p>Have availability for evenings and weekends</p></li></ul><p><strong>What will you do?:</strong></p><ul><li><p>Prepare ingredients and follow Sal's Gumbo Shack's signature recipes to create our renowned gumbo and other delectable dishes meticulously</p></li><li><p>Set up workstations with precision, ensuring all necessary ingredients, utensils, and equipment are readily available</p></li><li><p>Cook and present food in a timely manner, upholding Sal's Gumbo Shack's high quality and presentation standards</p></li><li><p>Collaborate seamlessly with the kitchen team to maintain the efficient flow of operations</p></li><li><p>Adhere rigorously to food safety and sanitation guidelines, guaranteeing a clean and organized work area</p></li><li><p>Monitor food inventory levels and actively contribute to inventory management</p></li><li><p>Assist in receiving, storing, and rotating ingredients and supplies to maintain freshness</p></li><li><p>Follow instructions from our esteemed Chefs, adapting recipes and techniques as needed</p></li><li><p>Contribute to the development of new menu items that reflect Sal's Gumbo Shack's culinary philosophy</p></li><li><p>Maintain a positive and professional attitude, thriving under pressure and fostering teamwork</p></li><li><p>Exhibit excellent time management skills, ensuring all orders are promptly completed</p></li><li><p>Take ownership of the cleanliness and maintenance of kitchen equipment, ensuring its</p><p>optimal performance</p></li><li><p>Continuously enhance culinary skills and knowledge through training and professional</p><p>development opportunities</p></li></ul><p><strong>Job requirements:</strong></p><ul><li><p>Strong understanding of food preparation techniques, culinary terminology, and operation of kitchen equipment</p></li><li><p>Proficiency in various cooking methods, such as slow cooking, stewing, and simmering, to achieve rich flavors</p></li><li><p>Familiarity with stringent food safety and sanitation regulations, maintaining a clean and hygienic environment</p></li><li><p>Ability to thrive in a fast-paced environment, juggling multiple tasks and prioritizing effectively</p></li><li><p>Keen attention to detail, consistently delivering the authentic taste and texture of Sal's Gumbo Shack's dishes</p></li><li><p>Excellent communication skills, collaborating seamlessly with colleagues in a tight-knit team</p></li><li><p>Availability to work evenings, weekends, and holidays, embracing the bustling nature of our restaurant</p></li><li><p>Physical stamina and the ability to stand for extended periods, comfortably lifting items up to 50 pounds</p></li><li><p>A culinary degree or relevant certification is a plus, highlighting your dedication to the craft</p><p>Join Sal's Gumbo Shack and become an integral part of our passionate team, as we continue to delight customers with our beloved gumbo and soulful cuisine. We offer competitive compensation, a vibrant work environment, and ample opportunities for growth within our esteemed restaurant. We appreciate all applicants, but only those selected for an interview will be contacted.</p></li></ul>]]></description>
    <posted_date><![CDATA[2023-06-01T16:53:31.527948Z]]></posted_date>
    <location>
      <zipcode><![CDATA[90805]]></zipcode>
      <city><![CDATA[Long Beach]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[CA]]></state>
    </location>
    <category></category>
    <discipline><![CDATA[hospitality]]></discipline>
    <employment_type><![CDATA[full_time]]></employment_type>
    <apply_method><![CDATA[website]]></apply_method>
    <apply_value><![CDATA[https://getgigs.co/jobs/efbaf799-27ae-4a9e-8178-73fd2fdc0daf]]></apply_value>
    <updated_datetime><![CDATA[2023-06-03T16:53:31.527948Z]]></updated_datetime>
    <workplace_type><![CDATA[on_site]]></workplace_type>
    <shift_type><![CDATA[day_shift]]></shift_type>
    <wage>
      <type><![CDATA[fixed_amount]]></type>
      <rate><![CDATA[hourly]]></rate>
      <minimum><![CDATA[25]]></minimum>
    </wage>
    <benefits></benefits>
  </job>
</provider>